http://www.wilburnmedical.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
**CLICK HERE for In Stock COVID-19 TESTS and PPE SUPPLIES**
Shopping Cart
Menu
Compare (0 Item)
1-336-996-6820
1-877-WILBURN  (1-877-945-2876)
Search
Categories
Medical Personal Protective Equipment (PPE)
Mononucleosis
Pregnancy (HcG)
Important Links
RentalsTraining and Resource Center:Cholestech LDXEquipmentCardioChekWUSA's Pro AdvantageSyringe PumpsCoaguChek XS PT/INRCoag-Sense PT/INRExam Room PlannerWUSA Universal IV TubingSiemens DCA VantageA1CNow - HbA1cHemoCueHemoPoint H2IV TherapyRapid DiagnosticsCorporate WellnessDiabetes Facts
WELLNESS
Corporate Wellness and Biometric Testing Equipment and SuppliesAUTOMATIC BLOOD PRESSUREBONE DENSITYFlu TestingPSA TestingTSH TestingCholesterol Testing*Cholestech LDX Rentals*Cardiochek Plus RentalsGlucose Testing*Siemens DCA Vantage RentalsHbA1c TestingSmoking Cessation (Cotinine)Drug TestingTraining VideosDopplersCLIA Information
GOT CLIA?
How to Obtain a CLIA Certificate Waiver Brochure
About
About Wilburn MedicalReviews
Shipping
W-9
Blog
Contact
HomePrivacy Policy
Categories
Medical Personal Protective Equipment (PPE)
COVID-19
COVID-19 Tests
Face Masks and Shields
Hand Sanitizer Bulk
Specimen Collection Viral Transport Medium VTM
Accepting Pre-Orders
Promotions
VidaShield UV24 Continuous UV-C Air Purification
Mononucleosis
Pregnancy (HcG)
Rapid Tests
RSV
Strep
Trichomonas Vaginalis
Urinalysis
Rapid Tests Alcohol Test
Rapid Tests Drugs Of Abuse Test
Rapid Tests Influenza
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for (http://wilburnmedical.com).  This privacy notice applies soley to information collected by this web stie.  It will notify you of the following:
1.  What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2.  What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3.  The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4.  How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Registration:
In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form.  During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address).  This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest.  At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not requred.
Orders:
We request informaiton from you on our order form.  To buy from us, you must provide contatct information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date).  This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders.  If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
Cookies:
We use "cookies" on this site.  A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site.  For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.  Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.
This website uses Google AdWords
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the wilburnmedicalusa.com website or e-mail submission. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you canopt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings orpermanently using a browser plugin.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing:
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site.  We only have access to information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  We will NOT sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information:
You may opt our of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
- See what data we have about you, if any.
- Change/correct any data we have about you.
- Have us delete any data we have about you.
- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security:
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.  You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline.  Only authorized employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-877-945-2876 or via email (Click Here).
Sign up for our Specials!
Name
Email
Copyright 2020 Wilburn Medical USA 1-877-945-2876. All Rights Reserved. | Sitemap |
Privacy Policy | Shipping Policies | Wilburn Medical W-9 Form
All prices are in USD
Connect with us
Wilburn Medical USA is a member of:
"So in everything, do to others what you would have them do to you, for this sums up the Law and the Prophets."
Matthew 7:12 (NIV)
Shipping Options:
